<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<doku>
  <key>email</key>
  <title>...and also Email ;)</title>
  <author>BloodHeart</author>
  <date>21.10.2012</date>
  <version>1.3</version>
  <lang>de</lang>
  <entry id="1"><![CDATA[[b]EMAIL[/b] is the function.

The ##botname## can send email to members that have registered their email address.
an email address should be deposited only then also if you often times ask from them.

##botname## keeps your data under wraps, of course, no one can or will receive from ##botname## called your address!

[u]save email addresses[/u]
If you want to save your address you can whisper the ##botname## or do in ally chat.
[quote]![b]email[/b] [i]addr[/i] bloodheart@online.ms[/quote]  Hotmail Emails dont work
##botname## confirmed, you can at any time change the address if you want to use a different address. 

[u]write email, but how?[/u]
If you would like to write email you can whisper the ##botname## or do in ally chat.
[quote]![b]email[/b] [i]bloodheart[/i] cheffe now take up the ass and come online![/quote]
This email will arrive, what happens then I dont say now :-w
You can use one of the aliases of a player so [quote]![b]email [/b] [i]blood[/i] sorry was not meant: d [/quote] also arrives;)

[u]can you reply to email?[/u]
to the time still not experimientiere I da still around.

[u]share email addresses with others  [/u]
##botname## assumes that everyone has its own address, try jamand to use it will not accept that your address.
If you however möchstest that eg. You can ##botname## that tell your partner, brother, sister or a familiar that uses the same address.
[quote]![b]email[/b] [i]multi[/i] on [/quote]
from then ##botname## admit it that uses your address to anyone else. 
with [quote]![b]email[/b] [i]multi[/i] from[/quote] you deactivate this function again.

[u]who may write me?[/u]
##botname## usually each Member of the ally allows you an email to write unless you not wish?
[quote]![b]email[/b] [i]do[/i] officers [/quote]
allows only still officers or higher you to write an email. It is also possible: [i]all officers (or shortly offi), management and alarm [/i].
alarm is a function only ##botname## which allows or in the special case of the direction, to send you a message. Alerts are further expanded, to the time it is only an idea.

you see you cant quite so, may I build a somewhat more comfort about the alsius tools ;)

have fun =)
]]>
  </entry>
</doku>